{
	"questions":
	[
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Knight",
		"answer": "Na aeket"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Knights",
		"answer": "Nek Aekechik"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Dog",
		"answer": "Na mwekane"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Dogs",
		"answer": "Nek mwekaneyok"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Cat",
		"answer": "Na pushis"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Cats",
		"answer": "Nek pushisak"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Fish (singular)",
		"answer": "Na names"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Fish (plural)",
		"answer": "Nek namesak"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Teacher",
		"answer": "Na sheshkulhalewes"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Teachers",
		"answer": "Nek sheshkulhalewesak"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Author",
		"answer": "Na ehelekhiket"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Authors",
		"answer": "Nek ehelekhikechik"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Crow",
		"answer": "Na ahas"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Crows",
		"answer": "Nek ahasak"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Bird",
		"answer": "Na chulens"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Birds",
		"answer": "Nek chulensak"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "Please",
		"answer": "Ksi"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "Thank you",
		"answer": "Wanishi"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "I'm sorry",
		"answer": "Nshielintam"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "Yes",
		"answer": "E-e"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "No",
		"answer": "Ku"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Car",
		"answer": "Ne amankshkinkw"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Cars",
		"answer": "Nel amankshkinkwe"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Cow",
		"answer": "Na wehshumwis"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Cows",
		"answer": "Nek wehshumwisak"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Pig",
		"answer": "Na kweshkwetet"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Pigs",
		"answer": "Nek kweshkwetetak"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Mouse",
		"answer": "Na pukwes"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Mice",
		"answer": "Nek pukwesak"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Storyteller",
		"answer": "Na Achimwis"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Storytellers",
		"answer": "Nek Achimwisak"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Horse",
		"answer": "Na Nehenaonkes"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Horses",
		"answer": "Nek Nehenaonkesak"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Wing",
		"answer": "Ne Lunkon"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Wings",
		"answer": "Nel Lunkone"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "Christmas",
		"answer": "Keleshmesh"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Animal",
		"answer": "Na Aeses"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Animals",
		"answer": "Nek Aesesak"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Train",
		"answer": "Ne Tente-tepchehelas"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Trains",
		"answer": "Nel Tente-tepchehelase"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Airplane",
		"answer": "Na Pemihelak"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Airplanes",
		"answer": "Nek Pemihelaksak"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Boat",
		"answer": "Ne Muxul"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Boats",
		"answer": "Nel Muxula"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Ship",
		"answer": "Ne Xinkwi Muxul"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Ships",
		"answer": "Nel Xinkwiyo Muxula"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The City",
		"answer": "Ne Utenay"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Cities",
		"answer": "Nel Utenaya"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Blue Jay",
		"answer": "Na Tiyas"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Blue Jays",
		"answer": "Nek Tiyasak"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The House",
		"answer": "Ne Wikewam"
	  },
		  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Houses",
		"answer": "Nel Wikwahema"
	  },
	  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Apartment",
		"answer": "Ne Wikhatuwikaon"
	  },
	  {
		"category": "Vocabulary",
		"question": "The Houses",
		"answer": "Nel Wikhatuwikaona"
	  }
	]
  }
  